splatf.com 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy - SplatF

This privacy statement covers SplatF.com.

 **Information Collection**

SplatF may collect information from our users at several different points on the site. SplatF is the sole owner of the information collected on SplatF.

 **Cookies**

SplatF may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. SplatF may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to SplatF. Persistent cookies can be removed. Consult your browser settings to remove cookies or prevent their usage.

 **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, SAY Media, our third-party advertiser, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. SplatF has no access to or control over these cookies. To [access SAY Media’s privacy policy](http://www.saymedia.com/privacy-policy.php), or to opt out of SAY Media targeting, [click here](http://www.saymedia.com/privacy-policy.php) and follow the instructions.

 **Log Files**

Like most websites, we use log files. These include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, SplatF may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process.

 **Links**

SplatF contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SplatF is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by SplatF.

 **Notification of Changes**

Whenever SplatF changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

 **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, please email the editor of SplatF, Dan Frommer, at hello@splatf.com.
